redtri.com 2019-07-20

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy was last updated on February 4, 2013.

**General**

  * Red Tricycle Inc. (“Red Tricycle”) respects your privacy and understands the concerns you may have regarding how we may use personally identifiable information.  This privacy policy identifies and describes the types of personally identifiable information we may collect from or about you when you visit the Red Tricycle website, how we use this information and when we share this information with third parties.  By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Red Tricycle.  You make the decision whether or not to proceed with any activity that requests personally identifiable information, but please be aware that if you choose not to provide the information requested, you may not be able to use certain features of our site or services.
  * Please read this privacy policy in its entirety.  We reserve the right to modify, alter, or otherwise update this policy at any time, and we encourage you to check back periodically so that you are always aware of the most current policies and practices that Red Tricycle has in place to protect your personally identifiable information.

**What Information Does Red Tricycle Gather About You?**

  * Personally Identifiable Information: We may collect personally identifiable information from you, including your name, email address, physical address, phone number, payment card information and gender when you engage in any of the following activities: order Red Tricycle products through our website; sign up to receive promotional materials via mail or email; or participate in a contest, promotion or survey.  Some of the personally identifiable information we collect from you, including your name, address, phone number, email address, and payment card information, is required in order to process your online purchases, respond to your requests, and contact you about your online purchases, if necessary.  We may collect information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, past experience with Red Tricycle products and services, detailed contact preferences or other personally identifiable information. We may also collect publicly available information about you from other sources, such as information from newspapers, blogs, and commercial websites or third party data aggregators; we may use such information to supplement your personally identifiable information maintained by us.  We may also collect personally identifiable information that you voluntarily disclose on the website, absent any request from us.
  * Automated Information: When you visit the Red Tricycle website, our web servers may automatically collect information that describes how our visitors use and navigate our website.  This information includes the number and frequency of visitors to each web page and the length of their stays, as well as the information that your web browser automatically sends to us, such as the date and time of your visit, your IP address, the web pages and images that you request, the search engine you used to access the website, previous websites you viewed, the type of Internet browser you use, the computer operating system you use.  Examples of other non-personally identifiable information that we may collect include your purchases, cookies, web beacons and information concerning your food preferences.  This enables us to enhance your browsing and shopping experience by tailoring information to fit your personal preferences.

**A Special Note About Cookies  **

  * Some pages of our website use cookies. Cookies are small pieces of software which are issued to your computer or device and which store and sometimes track information about your use of the site. By using the website you consent to our use of cookies as explained below.
  * Most of our cookies are necessary for operation of the website or service that you request as a user of the website, such as to remember login information, text you may have entered when you navigate back to a page in the same session. We also use cookies to provide optional features and functionality that you may access on the website. For example, a cookie can help us identify whether you have used our website in the past. We use cookies to customize and personalize the website based on preferences you may have expressed either directly by selecting an option or setting or indirectly by your prior use. We also use cookies that collect information about how you use the website to analyze and optimize the performance of the website in order to give you a better user experience. In some cases, particularly with respect to measuring and analyzing performance of the website, cookies may be placed by our third party service providers.
  * We and our third party partners may also employ web beacons, also known as clear GIFs or pixel tags, to help better manage content on the website. Web beacons are tiny, clear graphics that are embedded invisibly on web pages. They are used to understand and monitor online movements of users so that we may better understand and improve their experiences on the website. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are not stored on a user’s computer or device.
  * We may partner with a third party ad network to either display our advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner may use cookies, scripts, web beacons or other technology to collect information about your activities on this and other websites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.
  * We may analyze and share information collected through cookies with third parties, such as Red Tricycle’ subsidiaries, affiliates, business partners, service providers, and in marketing materials.
  * Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but, if you prefer, you may take certain steps to control the use of cookies by modifying your browser to reject cookies or to notify you whenever a cookie is sent to your hard drive. You can learn more about cookies and ways to manage them at <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>. Please be aware that restricting cookies on the website may impact the functionality and performance of the site.

**Content You Post  **

  * Please be aware that any messages, information or materials you post on our site are not private, are public, and are subject to the terms of this policy. Please do not submit any information to our site that you would like to be kept private or secure. We do not control or regularly review the messages, information or materials posted in the message boards. It is a condition of your use of the message boards and the website that you do not upload to, post, distribute or transmit to or through the website any messages, information or materials which violate or infringe in any way the rights of others, or which are libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, threatening, abusive, unlawful or would otherwise violate any law, or encourage such conduct, or which, without our express written consent, contains advertising or any commercial solicitation; post or transmit any material that contains a virus or other harmful component; restrict or inhibit anyone from using and enjoying the message boards.

**How Does Red Tricycle Use Your Information?  **

  * We may use information you provide to us for a variety of purposes, including the following: to process purchases, refunds, exchanges, and other transactions; to contact you about questions or communications regarding your order; to respond to your customer service inquiries; to contact you about new products, services, special events and promotions (unless you have elected otherwise in accordance with the “How Can You Access or Change Your Information?” section of this privacy policy): to help us learn about your shopping preferences; to help us improve our website, products, services and other offerings; and to otherwise enhance your shopping experience.
  * We may also share information that we collect, including personally identifiable information, with third parties to market Red Tricycle products to you. We do, however, provide our users a choice as to whether or not they would like to receive marketing or promotional communications. Users may also from time to time receive up-to-date information on products and services via our e-mail newsletter. Users may opt-out at any time from receiving these communications.
  * **Does Red Tricycle Share Your Information With Others?**
  * Except as described in this privacy policy, we do not sell, rent, lease or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information to third parties.
  * All personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information we collect about you may be shared with our affiliates, subsidiaries, distributors, retailers or marketers of Red Tricycle’ products, Red Tricycle’ partners and/or service providers who may be used to ship products, provide technical support, handle order processing, or otherwise act on Red Tricycle’ behalf for the purpose of marketing and providing Red Tricycle products, administering and operating the website and our business and sending marketing and promotional communications.
  * We may also share personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information about you with unaffiliated third parties that collect, manage, analyze or maintain data on our behalf, including website hosting service providers, payment processors, freight forwarders, carriers, companies that conduct or manage our marketing and promotional campaigns, and other third parties that perform services on our behalf (e.g., sending promotions and other communications and conducting contests and surveys).
  * We may also share your information with third parties when we believe such disclosure is required to (i) comply with laws, regulations and/or government policies; (ii) comply with court orders, legal processes, or government enforcement actions; (iii) establish or exercise our legal rights, protect our rights and interests and those of our other users, or defend against legal claims; or (iv) detect, investigate, prevent, or take action with respect to illegal activities, suspected fraud or misconduct, securities or technical issues, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of our terms of use or privacy policies.
  * In the event that we, or any of our affiliates or subsidiaries, are involved in a business transaction such as a merger, an acquisition, a consolidation, a reorganization, a liquidation, or any form of sale of all or a portion of our stock or assets, we may transfer your personally identifiable information to the buyer.

**How Can You Access or Change Your Information?**

  * You may access, review and edit the personally identifiable information that you provide to us online. You can also ask us to update your personally identifiable information or communication preferences by contacting us using the information provided in the “Contact Information” section of this privacy policy.  Please note that any request to update your information may take up to 30 days to process and that you may continue to receive communications from Red Tricycle using the previously provided information until your request becomes effective.
  * Additionally, you may opt-out from use of your personally identifiable information collected online for the purpose of sending such marketing or promotional communications at any time by following the unsubscribe instruction contained within each of the newsletters or promotional communications you receive.

**[How Does Red Tricycle Protect Your Information?]**

  *  Transactions placed online are processed through a third party vendor that uses Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) technology to protect your personally identifiable information.  SSL encrypts your order information, including your name, address, and payment card number before it is transmitted online.]
  *   * Of course, the security of any data transmission over the internet cannot be guaranteed, and any information that you transmit to us is at your own risk.

**Notification of Changes**

  * If we make any material changes that result in the use of personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will first attempt to notify you via e-mail and provide you with the choice as to whether or not you will allow us to use your information in this different manner. A notice will also be posted on our website notifying all users of the change.

**Does Red Tricycle Collect Information From Children Under the Age of 13?**

  * The Red Tricycle website is intended for general audiences and is not targeted to or intended for use by children.  We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen.  If we become aware that a child under the age of thirteen has submitted personally identifiable information through the Red Tricycle website without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove such information from our files.

**  Links To Third Party Sites**

  * While using this website, you may be linked or directed to other websites hosted by third parties.  For example, our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button Widgets and the “Share” button.  These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Red Tricycle does not control the dissemination of these cookies.  This privacy policy does not describe the information collection and disclosure practices of such third parties.  We do not control, and are not responsible for, the privacy practices and policies of such third parties or the content of these third party websites.  Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of those third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and policies of such third parties.

**United States Only**

This website is intended for users from the United States of America only. All matters relating to this site are governed by the laws of the State of California in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States and you contact us, please be advised that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States and that by submitting information you explicitly authorize this transfer and the processing of this information within the United States.  Any personally identifiable information that we collect from you will be treated in accordance with this privacy policy.

**  California Privacy Rights (For California Residents)**

  * California law gives California residents the right to ask us for a notice describing the categories of personally identifiable information we share with third parties or affiliates for their direct marketing purposes. The notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it has been shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please contact us through one of the communication methods described below in the “Contact Information” section.  Please allow 30 days for a response.

**  Acceptance of Privacy Policy**

  * By using the website, you signify your assent to our privacy policy. If you do not agree with this privacy policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of this website following posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

**Contact Information**

  * We are very sensitive to your privacy concerns and welcome your feedback.  Please contact our Customer Service Team at admin@redtri.com via email or at [415.729.9781](tel:415.729.9781) via phone if you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy.
